A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Evil monk Rasputin, you're mine. I'm gonna eat your soul.
You can try, but your effort will be wasted. Not even bullets can do any harm to me.
Guess it's a good thing I don't use bullets then. I hate wasted effort.
So, like I said, this Kishin egg soul of yours is about to be my dinner.
Souls are so yummy.
I hope it's a cool morning. That's how cool days always start out.
And a cool guy like me deserves the coolest morning possible.
Morning soul.
It's time for you to get up, sleepy boy.
Whoa! B-b-blair!
But there's no real hurry, right?
There we go. All done.
You could stay here and play with me today. We'll have some fun.
Soul, drag yourself out of bed and eat some breakfast. It's almost time for school.
Oh, good morning, Maka.
I have a feeling...
...that this particular morning...
...Soul.
Good morning, Maka.
I have a feeling...
that this particular morning...
Soul?
...is not gonna be cool at all.
繋いだ魂の火が 胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが 今 聞こえるか?
Sixx2
六人目も合わさず 運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル 食えない夜の端で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが
悪い夢に 続いても
繋いだ魂の火が 胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが 今 聞こえるか?
出会った訳は 途絶びに 引き付けられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ 確かになれる
死ぼ三者の間 悪杯
OUT
How many souls did you collect?
12. How many did you get?
So, Maka...
いふfruitな気持ち
dürfen俺とじめる?
メイけの必 sal抱 Saint
我 light you're so mad about
I'm not getting начmit
書面内に下化す
マーカー
ッ
Was there something you wanted to say?
It's about this rumor that's been going around.
You know that one teacher we used to have?
The one who died?
They found him with a Statue of Liberty sticking out of his brain.
Oh, you mean Sid and the Statue to the Forehead incident.
What about it?
You haven't heard?
They say there's some weird dude that's been coming after students from the Academy lately.
I guess some kid in the next class over got messed up pretty bad.
The point is, everyone who's seen this dude, they all say the same thing.
They say he was a zombie who had a hole in the middle of his forehead!
Did you really have to hit me again?
So your theory is that the zombie is Sid?
Please, it's only a story somebody made up to scare everyone.
All right, kids, quiet down.
Class is about to start.
I'm not going to bother taking attendance, but I will tell you one thing right now.
Anyone who thinks the bell decides when class is over is wrong.
I do.
Clear?
How was that, Maka?
Isn't your old man cool?
Hey.
Is it just me, or is that stupid father of yours making that goofy face right at us?
Um, I think it's just you.
Please do not refer to him as my father.
What's up with this death site?
Are you supposed to be our new teacher now or something?
I'm just a substitute until they find someone who can fill Sid's position permanently.
But that still means I'm in charge of this class.
So as long as I'm here, you will call me Professor Death Scythe.
All right, then.
Let's take attendance.
You said you weren't going to take role.
I'm not going to take attendance for the guys.
But I think I will for all the ladies.
Dammit, quit being a creep!
Oh, please.
Who doesn't know when to quit this one?
Soliter, Soliter.
Here it is.
For today, you get the lowest grade possible.
Okay, let's get this class started now.
Hey, old man, what did you just write down there?
Oh, that reminds me.
Maka and Sol.
What is it now?
Lord Death wants to see you in the death room.
You've been excused from class, so get going.
He wants to see us?
Engage the witch hunter.
A remedial lesson in the graveyard?
Hello?
I wonder why Lord Death wants to see us.
Who knows?
Look at Sol and Maka down there.
They think they can show their backs to me, do they?
Tsubaki, let's go.
Right.
Assassin's rule number one.
Dissolve in the darkness and erase your breath.
Wait for an opening to attack your target.
Oh, look.
It's Blackstar.
Why are you standing up there yelling like an idiot?
They found us pretty easily.
It can be real difficult to hide when you're as big a star as I am.
Oh, well.
That's a disadvantage I think I can handle.
Pretty big of me, huh, Tsubaki?
Oh, yes.
Seriously?
What are you doing here?
Were you guys called in to see Lord Death, too?
What if we were?
Here, I'll call him.
4242-564.
Whenever you want to knock on Death's door.
Lord Death, are you there?
Yeah, yeah.
Hi, hello.
What's up?
Thanks for coming.
Scythe Meister Maka reporting in.
Yeah, and Dark Arm Meister Blackstar, too.
And Tsubaki.
I'm his partner.
Well, what did you want with us?
Right.
I have a little assignment for you guys to take on.
Assignment?
Some extra lessons.
Huh?
Those extra lessons that stupid people get?
Those lessons?
Well, screw that.
I'm going to be a Death Scythe.
I'm way too cool for extra lessons.
Do you remember your duty as Meisters and weapons?
Yes.
Our duty as Meisters is to feed our weapons
99 Kishin souls and one witch's soul.
We collect evil souls in order to keep the world at peace.
We work to create a Death Scythe.
Weapon of the Grim Reaper, Death.
You are absolutely right.
But do you know how many souls all of you have managed to collect?
Exactly zero.
It isn't something to laugh about, Chuckles.
Anyway, are you ready to learn what your extra lessons will entail?
Maybe you've already heard the rumors?
About Sid, who taught here at the Academy until recently.
Sid, I was right.
It wasn't just a story.
Yeah.
But a zombie?
I always thought he was a really good teacher.
You're right.
When he was alive, he was regarded as an excellent teacher.
But when he became a zombie, he changed.
He has been released from the fear of death.
And now he wants others to have the same freedom he does.
He is trying to train students to free themselves as well.
But when a student won't listen, Sid attacks.
Another difficulty is that we still don't know who changed Sid into a zombie.
Or what their motive could possibly have been.
Okay.
You can leave it all to me, sir.
For our extra lesson, we just have to eliminate these guys?
Yep, that's pretty much it.
Now, I don't want to put too much pressure on you.
But if you happen to fail at these extra lessons,
then you're all going to be expelled.
What?
You're gonna kick us out?
There's nothing to worry about.
I can take care of guys like this in my sleep.
Come out!
Now time's over, zombie!
Hey, Tsubaki.
This is Sid's grave, isn't it?
Sure this is where we want to start looking?
Don't zombies get up and move around a lot?
Might as well check this place first
to be sure he isn't here.
I'm not gonna let myself get expelled over some walking...
It looks like an ordinary great stone to me.
Come out!
I never even listened to your lessons.
So there!
So soon.
A bit disturbed.
I always thought I was a great scythe-meister
like my mother was.
How can I suddenly be expelled?
What's up with Magda?
She seems kind of down.
Blackstar, aren't you at least a little worried about all this?
Where the hell are you hiding?
He's sold.
Why don't we go piss on Sid's grave?
What do you think about that?
Yeah, and while we're at it,
why don't we take a dump on it, too?
Come on, zombie.
Get out here.
Don't make us come find you.
We know you're around here somewhere.
Are you scared to find us?
I think you can stop me.
Maka!
Are you scared, girl?
Yeah.
I think you...
That's what Sid's become?
I guess so.
Maka, soul, blackstar, Tsubaki.
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Good night.
How have you been in all that?
I always tried to remember my manners.
That's the kind of man I was.
Tsubaki, let's get ready to end this guy.
Right.
And so it begins.
Tell me, Sid,
why are you doing this?
Ding, dong, dong, ding.
Being a zombie's amazing.
There are so many more things I can get away with now.
Class is in session.
I always was a man to start class right with the bell.
Punctuality is important.
This'll be fun.
I get to teach you a lesson now, teacher.
And since it's coming for me,
you know it'll be a big one.
We don't want to be expelled,
so we'll take your extra lesson.
But I gotta say,
I don't know what we're gonna learn
from a decaying piece of flesh.
If you become a zombie,
then death no longer looms over you.
You can escape from fear and be free.
That's wrong and you know it.
You were never the type of man who would say that.
And you'll understand when you're...
Blackstar,
there'll be no need to thank me for the lesson.
It's on the house.
I never was the kind of man...
Hold back!
I'd recommend you just give up.
You one-star Meisters don't have a chance of beating me.
I'm hungry!
Can we just get his damn zombie soul already?
Sid's right.
He is very strong.
One-star Meisters like us can't compete with him.
When he was alive,
he was designated a three-star Meister.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Hey, Sid,
if you keep swinging your tombstone around like that,
you might bang it into your fat head and die again.
It's my tombstone.
I can use it however I want, can't I?
Now then, kids,
it's time for second period.
Ding, dong, dong, ding.
Oh, yeah, I forgot to mention when this lesson is over,
you're all gonna die.
Then I guess we'll be cutting class today.
Think I'll go home and take a nice hot bath.
Maybe I should take some classes, too.
I bet Maka and Sol are having lots of fun right now.
What's wrong?
Why aren't you working together?
You have to establish a connection
between the souls of Weapon and Meister.
You're giving advice to the enemy?
I've always been an enthusiastic educator.
That's the kind of man I was.
And now I'll teach you how to die.
The living...
Black Star!
Sid was a Knifemeister.
But even without his blade,
the way he fights,
that tombstone is all he needs.
So this
is a three-star Meister.
Ding, dong, dong, ding.
Looks like class is over.
Ready to die yet, girl?
Well, what do you say?
Aren't you afraid of dying?
If you become a zombie,
then you'll be free from that fear of death forever.
Ugh, my head is killing me.
Your preaching is starting to give me a headache,
you damn zombie.
I'm not listening to any lesson of yours.
It doesn't matter what you say.
Who's gonna pay attention to a rotting corpse like you?
As long as there's a big star like me around!
Being a three-star Meister doesn't matter!
I am...
Black Star!
He aimed for the solar plexus,
the weakest point in the center of the body.
Hmm, that was a nice attack.
As one would expect from a dark assassin like Black Star.
Subaki!
Shuriken mode!
Right!
You can't run away!
As if I'd even try!
Maka, he's coming!
The living...
What the...
She avoided it with such a narrow margin for error.
People need fear to survive.
We experience it so that we can grow stronger!
Hmm?
Oh!
If she wasn't afraid in this situation,
I'd call that reckless.
But Maka has the courage to fight in spite of her fear.
Maka.
Let's do what he said.
See if you can match my soul's wavelength.
But that hasn't worked for us a single time before.
So what?
This is us.
We can do it.
Hmm.
Let's go!
Soul Resonance!
The legendary super skill of the Scythe Meister!
Witch Hunter!
You're trying to kill us?
What the hell, Marco?
Nice!
This is all your fault!
Do it right, idiot!
What?
You've got to be kidding me!
Why is this my fault?
You're the idiot here getting mad at me for nothing!
Die!
Die?
How can you say that?
That was incredible power!
You cry, baby!
I wanted to do it without a super skill!
I just wanted to do things that Scythe Meister might!
Huh?
He's gone.
No.
He's hiding underground.
He's down there?
Damn!
He dodged our attack again.
Now, Blackstar.
Yeah, I got it.
What Scythe's doing now is using the first of the Assassin's rules.
Dissolve in the darkness and erase your breath.
Wait for an opening to attack your target.
Tsubaki.
Let's get a step ahead of this guy.
Right.
You zombie bastard.
You're not going to upstage me in this performance.
Blackstar's movements seem different from usual.
Only one man is going to die in this graveyard.
But it's not going to be me.
Trapstar.
Assassin's rule number two.
Concentrate on the target.
If I listen carefully, I can hear his soul's wavelength.
I can pick it up through Tsubaki.
This breathing stopped.
And now?
Blackstar activate!
I think that it's about time to send you back to the grave.
You really stink.
What are you doing?
Tied me up along with this guy!
I wouldn't have to if you didn't get in my way.
So far, so good.
Maybe it's time to take a break from this.
So now they just have to find the person who turns Sid into a zombie, right?
That's right.
Who's responsible?
Do you know?
He's no ordinary enemy, is he?
You're familiar with my current weapon, right?
Death Scythe.
And I assume that you have at least heard of the Meister who trained him.
Yeah.
It was Maka's mother, wasn't it?
What about her?
Actually, that's not quite right.
Maka's mother was Death Scythe's second partner.
He had another.
So that means...
this person was his first.
Yes.
The man behind this is Dr. Frankenstein.
And not only was he Death Scythe's first partner,
he was also unquestionably the greatest Meister to ever graduate from the Academy.
I can't seem to get my head on straight.
I give up.
Too tired.
He's here.
We'll be right back.
Thank you.